So friends, if
₹1 has been credited to your account through IMPS, then this video
is for you. If you are confused as to why this ₹1 has been
credited to your account, then
definitely watch the video till the end. I am making
this video to clear your confusion. So
let's start the video.
You are watching it on the
official YouTube channel. First of all, let me
tell you
why ₹1 is credited to your account through IMPS. If you do
any financial activity, you
submit your account details to any app or any website, then
₹1 is credited to your account for verification
because it is done
through IMPS.
Friends, here the CAMS service
transfers ₹1 to your account for verification of your account,
due to which your account gets verified. So,
in this financial activity,
you have to open a limit account.  Or those
who apply for a loan or
any wing price, like you
register yourself in any team 11 up here, any mining price up,
then give your account details, then in
such a situation,
₹1 is credited to your account for verification.
What used to happen before this, friends, when you
manually registered your account in any up
or website or
submitted it, then due to
any digital mismatch in your account,
whatever amount was to be transferred in your account,
it could get transferred to some other account. For
this reason, CAM i.e.
Computer Access Management Service has been
launched, due to which your account is
immediately verified.
Like, if you register any account
in any website or up, then
here if your account has been
banned or frozen or has been
banned due to being very old, then ₹1 will not be credited to your account
and your account
verification  No, here you will
immediately get a message that your account has been
rejected. In this way, your
account is verified by dialing ₹1.
So I hope you have understood that
if ₹1 has been credited to your account through a pen drive
or from the Indian
Clearing Corporation, then
here you will
get it on the button of Video I.